Do you know where the kings and queens used to go to relieve themselves
?  I had brought my sisters to
a fort where the entire
wedding procession had disappeared.  You must have heard the name of Garh Kundar Fort.
By the way, I did not
make a full long vug of it.  Those who haven't
seen it yet, click on the link below and
watch it now.  This is the entrance of the fort.  Let me tell you that
this fort was built about 1500 years ago and the
loot from 52 different forts is
hidden inside it.  If we get that, the
whole country of India will become rich.  And
we had also come to see this.  And it was so dark that we got
separated from each other.  It is a blessing that the
government got the doors to its basement
closed.  Otherwise, no one would have been able to return home today.
Well, we climbed the steep stairs and
came up.  So here we saw the place from where the
other army was attacked and now I will
show you the place from where the
king and queen living in this palace used to defecate.
Sit at this place and the goods material is straight down
in the forest and before leaving, definitely check the long block.